Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ vandanabandaru (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Partnerships
Management
Enterprise Software

Languages

English Hindi

Vandana B

Founder and Managing Director at Infinitum Network Solutions Hyderabad

Summary

Vandana is a serial entrepreneur, who started her entrepreneurial journey in 2007 as CEO of Emorphosys, a software and digital solutions company and then went onto establish an online media firm called PortalApps. Together they are among the largest content partners to YouTube in SouthEast Asia with brands spread over various verticals like kids, learning, entertainment, cars and food. They also form the web's most diverse linguistic kids and learning network spread across 100 world languages. 17 billion views and 30 million subscribers stand testimony to the quality of the content that is completely developed in-house. The network has 9 channels above a million subscribers and more than 52 channels with more than 100,000 subscribers making it one of the most awarded "owned and operated" networks on YouTube.

Her latest venture Infinitum Network, is a social media marketing and digital advertising company, catering to some of the biggest production houses and talents in Tollywood apart from big brands globally.

She's a Masters in Business Administration with specialization in Finance from the prestigious Ohio University having extensive work experience in servicing large Fortune 500 companies, in her earlier stint as a wealth manager in world's foremost financial institution.

She's currently serving in various capacities as a Director, Managing Director and Chairman on board of 5 companies and is responsible for managing these companies' positioning, profitability and overall growth.

Known to be a digital native for years now, her specialities include social media strategy, digital creatives and content, e-learning, content creation, content strategy, celebrity management, brand building, influencer marketing, process implementation, with a strong hold of accounting and finance in addition to managing corporate alliances and partnerships globally.

Experience

Infinitum Network Solutions
Founder and Managing Director
April 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months)
India

Emorphosys
Chief Executive Officer
January 2007 - Present (13 years 8 months)
Hyderabad Area, India

PortalApps Media Solutions
Managing Director
August 2011 - Present (9 years 1 month)
Hyderabad Area, India

IndiGarage Automotive
Managing Director
June 2016 - Present (4 years 3 months)

Anvikshiki Publishers
Chief Publisher and Managing Director
March 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months)

www.edewcate.com Founder, CEO 2007 - Present (13 years)

CITIBANK Wealth manager 2005 - 2007 (2 years)

Education

Ohio University

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Finance · (2004 - 2006)